So let me come and click on this image and I click on edit image, yes?
So these are all the options that are available.
It seems like I can't do what I wanted to,
but let's try these, remove background, for example.
It's working on it.
Let's see how accurate it is when it comes to these tasks.
Yes, so for now, as you see, this is how it does it.
And we cannot do anything else with it.
Yep, we can change the color, but when it comes to blurring,
it says that your image does not have any background, so we can blur it.
Yep, this is pretty logical.
But I wanted to retouch it and, yeah, as I said,
it seems like we cannot edit an image using prompts or things like that over here.
So what about auto-enhancement?
I try it out.
Auto-enhance, yep.
And I'll wait a little bit.
Yes, we get a before after, as you see.
Nothing special happened so far.
Auto-enhance completed.
So, yep, we can...
I can't see the changes and the differences that I was looking for,
but auto-enhancement is possible, is also possible as you see.
And we can compare the before and the after,
and it says your image has been enhanced,
so we can either accept or discard the changes.
So that's what we have.
That's pretty much all that we currently have with the editor,
with the image editor of Microsoft Designer.
So I close this tab and I come back to the homepage.